legal things going on that can jeopardize your stay perhaps here in the United States. I just think that you're taking it like a trooper that you are. I think that you know that, you know, God is with you during this process.
in
in the
in the united
in the united states
in the united states i
in the united states i just
in the united states i just think
in the united states i just think that
in the united states i just think that you're
in the united states i just think that you're taking
in the united states i just think that you're taking it
in the united states i just think that you're taking it like
in the united states i just think that you're taking it like a
in the united states i just think that you're taking it like a trooper
in the united states i just think that you're taking it like a trooper that
in the united states i just think that you're taking it like a trooper that you
in the united states i just think that you're taking it like a trooper that you are
in the united states i just think that you're taking it like a trooper that you are i
in the united states i just think that you're taking it like a trooper that you are i think