and I put everything in God's hand, and you know, it wasn't easy, but I said, He got me this far. I know He's going to pull me too. So I just, you know, I just humble myself, and I call upon Him, man, and I just say, you know, every morning I get up, I say, Father, does God might go in and come in, you know?
easy
easy but
easy but i
easy but i said
easy but i said i'm
easy but i said i'm in
easy but i said i'm in this
easy but i said i'm in this far
easy but i said i'm in this far i
easy but i said i'm in this far i know
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon the
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon the body
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon the body men
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon the body men that's
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon the body men that's the
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon the body men that's the truth
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon the body men that's the truth every
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon the body men that's the truth every morning
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon the body men that's the truth every morning i
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon the body men that's the truth every morning i get
easy but i said i'm in this far i know it's going to be tough so i just doubled myself when i call upon the body men that's the truth every morning i get up