I think the hardest thing for you has been knowing that you still have some pending legal things going on that can jeopardize your stay perhaps here in the United States.
should
should i
should i be
should i be submitting
should i be submitting little
should i be submitting little things
should i be submitting little things going
should i be submitting little things going on
should i be submitting little things going on that
should i be submitting little things going on that gemini
should i be submitting little things going on that gemini should
should i be submitting little things going on that gemini should say
should i be submitting little things going on that gemini should say perhaps
should i be submitting little things going on that gemini should say perhaps the