Not Long Island. Which I kept thinking was Long Island. Which is dumb. And there was a moment when we were on the phone or FaceTiming or something. It was late at night.
which
which i
which i kept
which i kept thinking
which i kept thinking with
which i kept thinking with all
which i kept thinking with all this
which i kept thinking with all this and
which i kept thinking with all this and there
which i kept thinking with all this and there was
which i kept thinking with all this and there was a
which i kept thinking with all this and there was a moment
which i kept thinking with all this and there was a moment when
which i kept thinking with all this and there was a moment when we
which i kept thinking with all this and there was a moment when we were
which i kept thinking with all this and there was a moment when we were on
which i kept thinking with all this and there was a moment when we were on the
which i kept thinking with all this and there was a moment when we were on the floor