It's like one of my phobias, because it's just like, oh my God, there could be something right around that corner. I'm not going to check, like most people do in horror movies, where they're like here knocking on the door at like 12 o'clock, they check.
i'm
i'm not
i'm not going
i'm not going to
i'm not going to do
i'm not going to do that
i'm not going to do that like
i'm not going to do that like most
i'm not going to do that like most people
i'm not going to do that like most people do
i'm not going to do that like most people do in
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like either
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like either knocking
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like either knocking on
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like either knocking on the
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like either knocking on the door
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like either knocking on the door at
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like either knocking on the door at 12
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like either knocking on the door at 12 o'clock
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like either knocking on the door at 12 o'clock in
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like either knocking on the door at 12 o'clock in the
i'm not going to do that like most people do in horror movies like either knocking on the door at 12 o'clock in the night