So I really think it was a trip where you came down to Boston. We packed it up and we drove to New York. I made you pee in a bottle while listening to Beethoven blasting and then swerve the car.
so
so i
so i really
so i really think
so i really think it
so i really think it was
so i really think it was a
so i really think it was a dream
so i really think it was a dream you
so i really think it was a dream you know
so i really think it was a dream you know i
so i really think it was a dream you know i came
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i drove
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i drove to
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i drove to new
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i drove to new york
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i drove to new york city
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i drove to new york city and
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i drove to new york city and i
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i drove to new york city and i made
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i drove to new york city and i made it
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i drove to new york city and i made it over
so i really think it was a dream you know i came off the bus and i packed it up and i drove to new york city and i made it over and