Not Long Island. Which I kept thinking was Long Island. Which is dumb. And there was a moment when we were on the phone or FaceTiming or something.
it
it was
it was like
it was like i
it was like i kept
it was like i kept thinking
it was like i kept thinking with
it was like i kept thinking with long
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes and
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes and there
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes and there was
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes and there was a
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes and there was a moment
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes and there was a moment when
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes and there was a moment when we
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes and there was a moment when we were
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes and there was a moment when we were on
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes and there was a moment when we were on the
it was like i kept thinking with long eyelashes and there was a moment when we were on the floor