What's one experience you wish I never had? Your New York experience. I think anytime I think about that, especially if we're out and we've had a conversation you say I'm like overprotective kind of, but I think because of your New York experience, especially now that you're my fiance, like in my head it's drilled in like I need to protect you by any means necessary.
i
i don't
i don't know
i don't know two
i don't know two years
i don't know two years better
i don't know two years better i
i don't know two years better i think
i don't know two years better i think the
i don't know two years better i think the next
i don't know two years better i think the next time
i don't know two years better i think the next time i
i don't know two years better i think the next time i take