And not that my parents are the best example, but I mean, they dated for four weeks and they were married for 23, 24 years. So it's like I don't feel like I have to date you for X amount of years before I ask you to marry me. I think in the amount of time that we were together, I knew through all of our experiences together that this is what I want for the rest of my life.
my
my parents
my parents got
my parents got married
my parents got married at
my parents got married at the
my parents got married at the age
my parents got married at the age of
my parents got married at the age of 18
my parents got married at the age of 18 i
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were married
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were married for
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were married for 42
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were married for 42 years
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were married for 42 years it's
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were married for 42 years it's like
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were married for 42 years it's like i
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were married for 42 years it's like i don't
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were married for 42 years it's like i don't know
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were married for 42 years it's like i don't know for
my parents got married at the age of 18 i mean they dated for four years they were married for 42 years it's like i don't know for that