It's crazy as time passes. We just like really can't see one another. Yeah, and I get scared like You know, we're 22 now and it's hard to see each other. What happens when you're 22? And like in relationships or have kids or something maybe this is a relationship
getting
getting older
getting older is
getting older is crazy
getting older is crazy it's
getting older is crazy it's like
getting older is crazy it's like time
getting older is crazy it's like time passes
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we just
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we just get
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we just get really
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we just get really close
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we just get really close to
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we just get really close to one
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we just get really close to one another
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we just get really close to one another and
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we just get really close to one another and then
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we just get really close to one another and then get
getting older is crazy it's like time passes and we just get really close to one another and then get scared