It was about unicorns and clouds. It's Shane 2 AM today. You stopped crying. You were able to relax. So that one I do remember.
crying
crying it
crying it was
crying it was about
crying it was about like
crying it was about like you
crying it was about like you don't
crying it was about like you don't always
crying it was about like you don't always have
crying it was about like you don't always have to
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop crying
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop crying and
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop crying and you're
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop crying and you're able
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop crying and you're able to
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop crying and you're able to relax
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop crying and you're able to relax so
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop crying and you're able to relax so that
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop crying and you're able to relax so that will
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop crying and you're able to relax so that will get
crying it was about like you don't always have to yell but it actually works and you stop crying and you're able to relax so that will get you