At this point, I could care less. I don't think about when we were 10, 11 years old. Do I wish I had a friend with me and help me with school and, you know, help me get A's or just help me do better, man,
i
i couldn't
i couldn't get
i couldn't get this
i couldn't get this out
i couldn't get this out of
i couldn't get this out of my
i couldn't get this out of my mind
i couldn't get this out of my mind when
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school and
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school and could
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school and could call
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school and could call me
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school and could call me at
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school and could call me at night
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school and could call me at night or
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school and could call me at night or just
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school and could call me at night or just tell
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school and could call me at night or just tell me
i couldn't get this out of my mind when we were 11 and 12 years old so i wish i had a friend with me that had helped me with school and could call me at night or just tell me to